There was one band behind them all...
The Wrecking Crew is a music, documentary film directed by Denny Tedesco.
A celebration of the musical work of a group of session musicians known as "The Wrecking Crew." a band that provided
back-up instrumentals to such legendary recording artists as Frank Sinatra, The Beach Boys, and Bing Crosby.
Self - Producer, played by Lou Adler.
Self - Recording Artist Producer, played by Herb Alpert.
Self - Drums, played by Hal Blaine.
Self - Guitar, played by Glen Campbell.
Self - Guitar, played by Al Casey.
Self - Backup Singer, The Ronettes, played by Cher.
The Wrecking Crew is an American documentary film directed by
Denny Tedesco, son of guitarist Tommy Tedesco.
It covers the story of the Los Angeles–based group of session musicians known as the Wrecking Crew,
famed for having played on numerous hit recordings throughout the 1960s and early 1970s.
The film premiered at the 2008 South by Southwest Film Festival, although it
did not receive a commercial theatrical release until 2015.
The film explores themes of rock 'n' roll, musician, pop music.